A Guide to the David Rockefeller Personal and Professional papers, Memoirs, RG 7 FA790
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Research, 1906-2004; 3; 21.83 Cubic Feet 55 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes.
  - Chapter 35 - Africa (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 22 - The Bad Year (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 21 - The Bad Year (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Chapter 31 - Current Pursuits (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - DR Memoirs - Morningside Heights - Special Section (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Hawkers doc - Searching for Opportunities in Africa and Asia (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - DR14 (re Bilderberg) - DR's Draft, 1995 February 17 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Lost Illusions (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - New Chapter 16 - DR's Political Involvement in the 1960s (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Old Chapter 16 - Building the World Trade Center (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 1 - Grandfather (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 2 - Mother and Father (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 3 - Childhood (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 4 - Family Trips (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 5 - Rockefeller Center (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 6 - Harvard (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 7 - Studying Economics (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 8 - A Dissertation, A Wife, and a Job (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 9 - The War (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 10 - Embarking on a Career at Chase (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 11 - Launching a Parallel Career (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - RU Research for Chapter 11 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - XC11 New - Jack McCloy (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 12 - Building the Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 13 - Conflict (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 14 - Difficult Transitions (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 15A - Creating a Global Bank (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 16 - Taking the Helm (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 17 - Engaging the Soviets (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 19A - Emissary for "Balance" in the Middle East (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 18AA - Penetrating the Bamboo Curtain (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 20A - Surviving OPEC (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 21 - Business Turbulence (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 22 - Family Turmoil (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  - Chapter 23 - Brotherly Conflicts (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
  - Chapter 24 - "The Shah" and Background Material (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
  - Chapter 25 - Redemption (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs - Notes of Conversations (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Memoirs - Notes on Interviews '89, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Memoirs - Harvard, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Memoirs - London School of Economics (LSE), 1940-1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Memoirs - Economic and Economists (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Economics - Theories - Berger Capitalism and Development (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Memoirs - Religion and Social Gospel (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - David Rockefeller - WWII - T-Force - "From Stausbourg to Munich" (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Memoirs - Transcripts (Box 36, Folder 1-7, Box 37, Folder 1-6)
  - Clearing House Committee and Community Preservation Corporation (CPC), 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - New York City (NYC) - Westway (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Memoirs - Turkey and Cyprus (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Third World Trips, 1985 Summer (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Photocopied source material from Chase Manhattan Bank.
  - Middle East - 1969-1980 - David Rockefeller Memos (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Trips to Asia and China, 1970s-1990s (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
  - Letters - David Rockefeller and JDR Jr., 1940-1959 (Box 38, Folder 4-6)
  - Letters - Peggy Rockefeller and JDR Jr., 1940-1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Letters - Peggy and David Rockefeller - including with Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1930s-1940s (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - JDR Jr. and David Rockefeller, 1933-1960 (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence - JDR Jr. and David Rockefeller, 1920-1929 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Letters - JDR Jr and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1921-1944 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Letters - David Rockefeller to Parents, 1925-1928 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Correspondence, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - JDR Jr. and David Rockefeller, 1930s (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - JDR Jr. and David Rockefeller, 1940s-1950s (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller - Correspondence, 1920s (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - David Rockefeller - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  - David Rockefeller - Lincoln School and Childhood, 1920s-1980s (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence - Peggy and David Rockefeller with JDR Jr., 1950-1959 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Peggy and David Rockefeller Wedding - Guests, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller - Harvard University, 1985-1987 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Philanthropy, 1947-1984 (Box 41, Folder 6-7, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Chase Manhattan and the Urban Environment Report, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Economic Development, 1965-1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Peterson Commission, 1966-1970 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - South Africa, 1965-1985 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - David Rockefeller - Western Trips, 1915-1986 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Latin America - Philanthropy and Debt, 1970s-1980s (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Europe - Process of Integration, 1919-1973 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Trilateral Commission, 1982-1991 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Management History, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Bilderberg, 1954-1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), 1967-1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Bohemian Grove, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Horace Albright Correspondence, 1924-1987 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc. (RBI) - 1952 Annual Report, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Pocantico Planning Project - Final Report, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - A Social Audit for Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Leaders Magazine - David Rockefeller Cover Story, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - David Rockefeller - The Evolution of Management Thought, 1970s-1980s (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - David Rockefeller and Corporate Philanthropy, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Standard Oil and Competition from Russia (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR) - John J. McCloy - "Reflections" Draft, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1946-1967 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology - Trips, 1977-1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller Trip to Jamaica - Department of State Briefing Book, 1983 November 5-6 (Box 44, Folder 4A)
    Restricted - Confidential material
  - Press Clippings for Memoirs, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 5-6, Box 45, Folder 1-6, Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - David Rockefeller - Press Clippings, 1970s-1991 (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
  - David Rockefeller - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), 1941-1985 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Embarcadero Center, 1967-1974; 1991 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - New York City Fiscal Crisis, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Brazilian Presidents, 1946-1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Trips - Africa, 1959; 1982; 1984 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Agricultural Mission to Poland - Report to Rockefeller Foundation and Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF), 1982 December (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Chase Dinner in honor of Thai Prime Minister, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - David Rockefeller - Correspondence with Parents, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Joint Intelligence Collection Agency - Copies of Reports from National Archives, 1940s-1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Peter Johnson Notes on Visit to National Archives in 1984 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller - Military Service, 1940s (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - David Rockefeller - Military Service - Army Reserve, 1945-1954 (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Report to the Board of Managers, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Chase - International Expansion, 1950-1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - David Rockefeller Interviews - Memoirs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology - Latin America, 1940s-1950s (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Political Contributions, 1970s (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - "Impressions of China" - Gerald Curtis, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Future of the Office - 1970s-1980s - Memos (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Office Organization and Procedures, 1949-1966 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - World Management Council, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Mitch Feigenbaum - Chaos Theory, 1981-1987 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Cary Reich - NAR Biography, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Salles Manuscript of David Rockefeller Interview, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - CIOS - World Management Council, 1989 September (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - North American Management Council (NAMCO), 1990 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Charles de Gaulle Interview, 1989 March (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Pentagon - Roger Pearce, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Wally Nielsen, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Research Request, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - American University in Cairo, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Seymour Topping and George Santayana, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Baron Lambert, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth Cobbs, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Pounds - Office Study, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Awards - Order of the Sacred Treasure (Japan), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Wylie, 1989-1993 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Cloisters - Barnard Collection (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller International House, 1950 April 29 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller - New York City Background of International House, 1950 April 4 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Memoirs - Chase Manhattan Bank (CMB) History (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs - Chase Purchases, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Memoirs - Chase Manhattan Bank (CMB) - Legal, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Memoirs - Chase Manhattan Bank (CMB) - General Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller - Contributions to MoMA, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - David Robarge, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Background Information (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Urban Development with Warren Lindquist, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Education Background (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Housing Interests (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Initial Thoughts and Ideas (JD Memo), 1987 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Inter-American Relations (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Location of Materials, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Outline (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Philanthropy (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Memoirs - Errors, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Memoirs - Special Letters of Recognition, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Memoirs - Letters File, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Planning for 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Publicity, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Memoirs - 20/20 Segment, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs - ArtNews Kelly Devive Thomas, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Memoirs - Bangor Daily News (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Capital Magazine (Chile) Javiera Maragua (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Memoirs - Charlie Rose Show, 2002 October 21 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Memoirs - Chicago Sun Times, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Memoirs - Corriera della Serra, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Memoirs - ABC Magazine, Christina Callo, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Memoirs - Interview El Mundo, Maria Ramirez and Miguel Rajmal, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Memoirs - Famiglia, Christine Guilia Cerquet, 2003 February 13 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1977-1982 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Harvard, 1932-1960 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Harvard Material, 1933-1987 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Harvard - Classes, 1932-1964 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - David Rockefeller Material, 1920s-1940 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Interviews, 1980s (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller and BF Goodrich, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - New York City Housing Partnership Study, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - John Maynard Keynes (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Harold Laski (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Interviews with David Rockefeller, 1984-1987 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Trip to Japan, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Visit to South Africa, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Fazenda Bodaquena, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Margaret M. Rockefeller - Biographical Data (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - IESC - Breakthrough Program, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank - Government of Singapore, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank - Chase Manhattan International Foundation, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Philanthropic Activities of Chase Manhattan Bank, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Philanthropy Articles, 1980s (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - MoMA - Paley and Stein Collections, 1984-1992 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - NEA and NEH - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - General Files, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - National Medal of Arts, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Trilateral Commission, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller Political Contributions, 1985-1992 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Collier and Horowitz (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Memoirs - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Harvard - Economics - Schumpeter (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - David Rockefeller Trips, 1948-1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Ecuador Trips, 1948-1985 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Hugh Morrow - Interview of David Rockefeller (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Pocantico Plan, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - David Rockefeller and JDR Jr., 1930-1936 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - David Rockefeller and JDR Jr., 1935-1939 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - David Rockefeller and Shah of Iran, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller - Diaries, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller - Chase - Creative Philanthropy, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - David Rockefeller - Trips to China, 1973-1988 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller - World War II, 1940s (Box 54, Folder 4A)
  - David Rockefeller - Creative Management Banking (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller - Guiding Principles (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - David Rockefeller - Interviews - Aunt Lucy, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - David Rockefeller - Interviews - Turkey, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - David Rockefeller - Interviews - Gorbachev, Poland, Walesa, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - David Rockefeller - Interviews - Ford and Casey, Harvard, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - David Rockefeller - Interviews - Chase Crisis, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - David Rockefeller - Interviews - New York City Bank Crisis, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - United States Banking History (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - New York City 1920s (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Mount Desert and Bar Harbor (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Chase Chronology 1945-1985 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Peter Robinson, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Americas Society - History, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - David Rockefeller Letters, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Fund, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - New York City (Excerpts from Books) (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Heinemann, Erich, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Jack McCloy, Interview with Max Holland, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Osmond Interview, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Albright's Memoirs, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association (D-LMA), 1990 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Abeyton Lodge, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Dillon Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - John Haley - Interview, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Bill Ogden - Interview, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Robert Armao, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Banking Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - David Rockefeller Associations and Organizations, 1981; 1991 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - 146 East 65th Street, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - John Millman - Forbes, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Columbia Oral History, 1972; 1991 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Ideas on Memoirs, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - JDR 150th Anniversary, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Americas Society / Council of Americas History (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1940s-1950s (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Community Preservation Corporation, 1970s (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Urban Affairs - Timeline, 1946-1960s (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - JDR Jr's Model Housing Activities (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Letters - JDR 3rd and David Rockefeller, 1930s-1940s (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Urban Coalition, 1960s-1970s (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Memoirs - Fujisankei Communication, 2002 September 11 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Investors Business Daily, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Asian Brochure, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Milenion (Brazilian TV), 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Panorama Magazine, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - People Msgazine, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Geraldo Grecco, RAI-Italian TV, 2002 December 16 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sotheby's - Rockefeller and Co. Event at Sotheby's, 2003 May 20 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Valor Magazine, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Vanity Fair, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Declines, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Schedule and Itineraries, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Chase Reception, New York City, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - 92nd Street Y, New York City, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Chicago, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), New York City, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - The Century, New York City, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Houston, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Historic Hudson Valley, Westchester, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Kansas City, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Maine, 2003-2004 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Philadelphia, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - RU Launch, New York City, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - San Diego, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - San Francisco, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Memoirs Book Tour - Washington D.C., 2002 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Memoirs - Soft Cover Book Tour, Preliminary Information, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Memoirs - Andrew Wylie Catalogue Photos, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Book Design, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Random House Catalogue Copy, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - David Rockefeller Memoirs - Random House Cover Photo, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Memoirs - Gifts of Proceeds, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Memoirs - Revisions and Paperback Edition (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Memoirs - Marketing, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Memoirs - Brazilian Edition, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Memoirs - Bulgarian Edition, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Memoirs - Chinese Edition, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Memoirs - Italian Edition, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs - Korean Edition, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Memoirs - Serbian Edition, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Memoirs - Russian Edition (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Memoirs - Spanish Edition, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Memoirs - Taiwanese Edition, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Memoirs - Foreign Rights, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Memoirs - Eaton Press Edition, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Memoirs - Book Endorsements, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Memoirs - Publication Photo Rights, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Memoirs - Subsidiary Rights, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Memoirs - Soft Cover Preliminary Tour Dates, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Memoirs - Soft Cover Copy Change, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Memoirs - Andrew Wylie Catalogue Advance, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Memoirs - Copy, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Memoirs - Josh Gilder, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 22)